outreachtime.com 2012-02-28

# Privacy Policy - Web-based IEP, Direct Service, Time Study Software from Bretch's Database Solutions

###  **< Return To Log In**

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.outreachtime.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following: 

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  2. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  3. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**  
The information we collect regarding you is supplied by member districts. It consists of your e-mail address, first and last name. 

We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization and its subsidiaries. 

We may contact you via email in the future to tell you about software updates, legal issues, or changes to this privacy policy. 

**Cookies**  
We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you we can track what files were accessed and changed. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site. 

**Security**  
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. 

Wherever we collect sensitive information, that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page. 

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. 

If you feel the information we have is incorrect, it is your responsibility to contact your employer to have them update that information. 

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 888-437-9326 or via email at [support@outreachtime.com](mailto:support@outreachtime.com). 

###  **< Return To Log In**
